现在我们有了数据库，我们可以利用好
Now that we have a database, we can take
Android的模式，将作为应用content provider的数据
advantage of an Android pattern to bind our view to
和界面连接起来
our data model known as a content provider. A content
content provider让我们想到数据
provider allows us to think of our view data in
就我们的 URL 而言，是一个适合我们应用的结构
terms of URIs which is a convenient structure for
我们可以显示不同的数据，来源于
our applications. We can have views display different data based
那些当前活动的URL。事实证明
upon which URI is currently active. As it turns out,
URL是这些Intents的主要数据成员
a URI is the primary data member for those Intents,
通过content provider和intents相结合
that Rato so gloriously described. With a combination
我们可以很方便地
of content providers and intents, one can nicely
将数据从视图中分离开来
decouple the data being displayed from the view.
使用URL和data location
And there's one other great thing we get from
我们可以从中得到一件更棒的事情。
using URI with a data location. It's easy
这很容易让我们的数据库中注册用来观察location的通知部件
to have our database notify components that are registered
location的变化导致我们的光标去更新列表
to observe that location which causes our cursor
并且展示最新的数据
to update our list and show the latest data.
content provider会返回各种数据，但通常是，他们返回
Content providers can return all sorts of data but typically, they return either
的是一个列表，或者是一个单一列表项。这里是我们如何修改
a list of items, or a single item. Here's how one might modify our
去选择一个特定的日期的数据，而不是一定范围内的天数
query to select the data for a specific date, rather than a range of
在这种情况下包含了更多可以显示出来的信息
days which in this case also contains more information for the viewer to see.